Guide to the John L. Hennessy, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0700
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- President's records, 2005-2006; Accession ARCH-2008-057
  - National Science Foundation, 10/18/2005-06/22/2006; G 3.19 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Local Government, 09/06/2005-05/23/2006; G 4 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Foreign Government Relations, 10/04/2005-05/22/2006; G 5 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - CIFPR, 11/02/2005-08/22/2006; G 7 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Stanford in Government, 04/20/2006; G 8 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 09/12/2005-08/18/2006; G 10 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Lucile Packard Children's Hospital, 01/18/2005-06/12/2006; SHS 7 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Medical Organizations, Misc., 05/09/2006-05/30/2006; SHS 8 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - HHMI, 11/21/2005-04/06/2006; SHS 9 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - School of Medicine Admin., 03/19/2003-07/11/2006; M 1 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - School of Medicine Dev., 08/30/2006; M 2 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - School of Medicine Depts., 10/03/2005-08/08/2006; M 5 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Misc. Organizations (1 of 4), 10/25/2004-12/05/2005; O 1 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Misc. Organizations (2 of 4), 12/05/2005-03/27/2006; O 1 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Misc. Organizations (3 of 4), 04/04/2006-05/17/2006; O 1 (Box 6, Folder 148)
  - Misc. Organizations (4 of 4), 05/19/2006-08/29/2006; O 1 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Education Groups, (Outside Misc.), 11/01/2005-08/01/2006; O 3 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - COFHE, 09/05/2005-08/15/2006; O 3.1 (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - APRU, 10/24/2005-08/30/2006; O 3.4 (Box 6, Folder 152)
  - AAAS (1 of 2), 12/11/2001-05/22/2006; O 3.7 (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - AAAS (1 of 2), 06/16/2006-08/28/2006; O 3.7 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - American Council on Education, 09/01/2005-08/21/2006; O 3.8 (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - NAICU, 10/18/2005-08/21/2006; O 3.10 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - The College Board, 09/12/2005-08/30/2006; O 3.25 (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - The National Academies, 09/09/2005-06/28/2006; O 3.43 (Box 6, Folder 158)
  - NCAA, 09/06/2005-08/22/2006; O 3.44 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Business Higher Education Forum, 09/19/2005-07/24/2005; O 3.56 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Athletic Organizations, Misc., 12/14/2005-08/09/2006; O 4 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Research Organizations, Misc., 03/13/2006-05/01/2006; O 7 (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - Universities Research Association, 09/20/2005-07/07/2006; O 7.16 (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - Universities & Colleges, Misc. (1 of 4), 09/10/2002-11/14/2005; O 8 (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - Universities & Colleges, Misc. (2 of 4), 11/28/2005-03/21/2006; O 8 (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - Universities & Colleges, Misc. (3 of 4), 03/23/2006-05/30/2006; O 8 (Box 7, Folder 166)
  - Universities & Colleges, Misc. (4 of 4), 05/31/2006-08/28/2006; O 8 (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - AAU, 10/24/2005-06/16/2006; O 8.7 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - AICCU, 09/14/2005-05/26/2006; O 8.9 (Box 7, Folder 169)
  - California State Universities, 01/11/2006-03/31/2006; O 8.17 (Box 7, Folder 170)
  - Columbia University, 04/20/2006; O 8.18 (Box 7, Folder 171)
  - Harvard University, 06/23/2005-06/27/2006; O 8.23 (Box 7, Folder 172)
  - Princeton University, 10/17/2005-03/16/2006; O 8.36 (Box 8, Folder 173)
  - University of California, 01/12/2005-06/16/2006; O 8.43 (Box 8, Folder 174)
  - University of Southern California, 02/23/2006-06/21/2006; O 8.49 (Box 8, Folder 175)
  - Yale University, 06/2001-06/05/2006; O 8.53 (Box 8, Folder 176)
  - Inaugurations (Other Schools), 09/01/2005-08/30/2006; O 8.55 (Box 8, Folder 177)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum, 09/26/2005-08/28/2006; O 11 (Box 8, Folder 178)
  - Vice Provost & Dean of Research, 10/13/2005-08/23/2006; R 0 (Box 8, Folder 179)
  - Freeman Spogli Institute, 10/24/2005-01/27/2006; R 1.12 (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Students, Misc., 09/20/2005-08/14/2006; ST 1 (Box 8, Folder 181)
  - Student Groups, Misc., 09/16/2005-08/11/2006; ST 1.1 (Box 8, Folder 182)
  - Haas Center for Public Service, 04/25/2005-04/13/2006; ST 3.29 (Box 8, Folder 183)
  - John Gardner Fellowship, 06/19/2006-06/20/2006; ST 3.29/1 (Box 8, Folder 184)
  - Campus Compact, 09/22/2005-08/03/2006; ST 3.35 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Parent/Student Correspondence, 01/05/2005-12/13/2005; ST 8 (Box 8, Folder 186)
- President's records concerning WASC, 2008; Accession ARCH-2008-251
  - Institutional Proposal for Reaccreditation by the Western Association of Schools and Colleges, 2008 May 15 (Box 1)
  - Appendices for the Institutional Proposal for Reaccreditation by the Western Association of Schools and Colleges, 2008 May 15 (Box 1)
- President's records, 2006-2007; Accession ARCH-2009-080
  - Provost's Office, 09/12/2006-03/19/2007; AA 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dean of Chapel, 01/30/2007-06/05/2007; AA 1.8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Emeriti, 02/08/2007-08/13/2007; AA 2.2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Development/Affairs, 08/22/2006-05/18/2007; AA 2.7 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate Education, 02/01/2007-03/15/2007; AA 3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Accreditation Issues, 09/05/2006-06/06/2007; AA 3.4 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ratings/Rankings, 11/03/2006-08/15/2007; AA 3.5 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Cultures, Ideas & Values, 09/13/2006-01/30/2007; AA 3.5.1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Continuing Studies, 01/03/2007-03/18/2007; AA 3.6 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Summer Programs, 01/24/2007-05/15/2007; AA 3.16 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Humanities & Sciences, School of, 09/05/2006-08/02/2007; AA 4.1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Humanities Center, 09/06/2006-06/19/2007; AA 4.1.1/2 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - MLK, Jr. Research & Education, 06/28/2007-08/27/2007; AA 4.1.1/3 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Applied Physics, Dept. of, 04/10/2007; AA 4.1.8 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Art, Dept. of, 09/18/2006-05/12/2007; AA 4.1.9 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Chemistry, Dept. of, 05/18/2007-05/18/2007; AA 4.1.13 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Computer Science, Dept. of, 10/06/2005-06/28/2007; AA 4.1.17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Drama, Dept. of, 10/31/2006-01/24/2007; AA 4.1.18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - SIEPR, 09/12/2006-08/27/2007; AA 4.1.20/1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - English, Dept. of, 09/20/2006-12/08/2006; AA 4.1.21 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Program in Writing and Rhetoric, 10/27/2006-10/30/2006; AA 4.1.26 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Music, Dept. of, 10/09/2006-06/01/2007; AA 4.1.29 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Athletics, Dept. of (1 of 3), 01/03/2005-01/04/2007; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Athletics, Dept. of (2 of 3), 01/05/2007-03/14/2007; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Athletics, Dept. of (3 of 3), 03/14/2007-08/15/2007; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Football Games, 09/15/2006-10/10/2006; AA 4.1.30/1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Political Science, Dept. of, 11/29/2006-12/18/2006; AA 4.1.34 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Psychology, Dept. of, 09/07/2006-06/27/2006; AA 4.1.35 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - GSB, 09/07/2006-08/29/2007; AA 4.2 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - GCEP, 03/26/2007-10/02/2007; AA 4.3.1 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Engineering, School of, 08/17/2005-07/05/2007; AA 4.4 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Education, School of, 12/06/2006-06/19/2007; AA 4.5 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Hoover Institution, 09/11/2006-05/18/2007; AA 4.9 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - CISAC, 12/06/2006-08/29/2007; AA 4.10.6 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - SULAIR, 09/19/2006-08/28/2007; AA 4.12 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Law, School of, 09/05/2006-10/02/2006; AA 4.15 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - IT Services & Admin. Systems, 09/27/2006-06/05/2007; AA 4.22 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Awards & Prizes, Misc., 09/05/2006-08/30/2007; AA 5 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 03/26/2007; AA 5.2 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Grants & Scholarships, Miscellaneous, 09/01/2006-08/27/2007; AA 6 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Fellowships, Miscellaneous, 12/12/2005-08/28/2007; AA 8 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Fulbright Fellowship/Scholarships, 03/12/2007-08/29/2007; AA 8.16 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Knight Fellowships/Foundation, 02/12/2005-08/28/2007; AA 8.25 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Tanner Lectures, 07/17/2007; AA 9.19 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Faculty/Prof. Chairs, 10/19/2006-12/12/2006; AA 10 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Stanford Miscellaneous, 09/09/2005-08/23/2007; AD 1 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - ROTC, 01/18/2007-07/26/2007; AD 2.26 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - President's Office, 09/13/2006-05/15/2007; AD 4 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Holiday Cards (1 of 2), 12/04/2006-12/18/2006; AD 4.20 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Holiday Cards (2 of 2), 12/19/2006-01/11/2007; AD 4.20 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence, General, 03/29/2006-08/14/2007; AD 4.20 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - News articles, 09/21/2006-08/07/2007; AD 4.20.1 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Condolence Letters, 12/30/2005-07/05/2007; AD 4.20.2 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 01/03/2002-07/02/2007; AD 4.20.3 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Appreciation Letters, 10/19/2005-08/27/2007; AD 4.20.4/1 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Invitations (1 of 3), 12/09/2005-12/04/2006; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Invitations (2 of 3), 12/04/2006-04/30/2007; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Invitations (3 of 3), 05/01/2007-08/31/2007; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Nonsense, 08/01/2006-08/20/2007; AD 4.20.5 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Recommendation Letters, 11/10/2006-08/14/2007; AD 4.20.6 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Complaint Letters, 09/05/2006-08/07/2007; AD 4.20.7 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Solicitations (1 of 4), 04/12/2006-11/20/2006; AD 4.20.8 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Solicitations (2 of 4), 11/20/2006-12/20/2006; AD 4.20.8 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Solicitations (3 of 4), 01/05/2007-05/07/2007; AD 4.20.8 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Solicitations (4 of 4), 05/07/2007-08/27/2007; AD 4.20.8 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Admissions, 09/05/2006-08/27/2007; AD 8.1 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Student Affairs, 09/18/2006-07/17/2007; AD 8.8 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Vaden Health Center, 01/24/2005-03/20/2007; AD 8.9 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Bing Overseas Studies, 10/19/2006-05/15/2007; AD 8.11 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Financial Aid, 09/11/2006-06/27/2007; AD 8.12 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, 12/30/2003-08/15/2007; AD 8.18 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Hanna House, 11/28/2006-01/29/2007; AD 8.18.2 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Residential & Dining Enterprises, 09/15/2006-05/30/2007; AD 8.18.11 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Human Resources, 09/07/2006-06/01/2007; AD 10 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - SLAC/CLJ, 10/05/2006-08/06/2007; AD 10-SLAC/CLJ (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Employment Inquiries, 09/20/2006-08/27/2007; AD 10.1 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Events, Stanford and Public, 09/20/2006-04/20/2007; AD 11.7.5/1 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Lively Arts, 09/11/2006-06/20/2007; AD 11.7.5/2 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Freshman Issues, 09/22/2006-07/11/2007; AD 11.7.7 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Media & Publications Misc. (1 of 3), 09/06/2006-08/09/2007; AD 11.8 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Surveys, Questionnaires, 09/05/2006-08/27/2007; AD 11.8.10 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Media & Publications (internal), 08/31/2006-07/09/2007; AD 11.8.11 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Tuition, 10/20/2006-04/05/2007; AD 12.5.4 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Office of Development, 12/19/2006-05/18/2007; AD 12.10.1 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - The Stanford Fund, 10/10/2006-05/18/2007; AD 12.10.2/3 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Asian Relations, 09/18/2006-08/13/2007; AD 12.10.2/9 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Land, BLDGS & Real Estate, 10/11/2006-07/12/2007; AD 12.14 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Stanford Bookstore, 09/14/2006-02/23/2007; AD 12.14.7/5 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Conferences, Misc. (1 of 2), 09/15/2006-08/15/2007; AD 13.10.1 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Alumni Relations, 09/05/2006-07/21/2007; AL 1 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Stanford Parents Club, 11/27/2007-02/01/2007; AL 1.1/1 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Alumni Correspondence, 09/12/2006-08/14/2007; AL 1.3 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - U.S. Government, 09/06/2006-08/15/2007; G 3 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Defense, Dept. of, 09/08/2006-06/27/2007; G 3.7 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Energy, Dept. of, 09/19/2006-07/24/2007; G 3.7.2 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Education, Dept. of, 11/14/2006-08/29/2007; G 3.8.3 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - National Science Foundation, 10/19/2006-07/06/2007; G 3.19 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Foreign Government Relations, 10/04/2006-08/27/2007; G 5 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - CIFPR, 09/08/2006-08/16/2007; G 7 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 10/17/2006-07/20/2007; G 10 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Lucile Packard Children's Hospital, 08/08/2006-08/15/2007; SHS 7 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - School of Medicine Admin., 09/05/2006-08/23/2007; M 1 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Misc. Organizations (1 of 2), 04/02/2002-03/20/2007; O 1 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Misc. Organizations (2 of 2), 04/05/2007-08/28/2007; O 1 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Education Groups (1 of 2), 08/03/2006-02/05/2007; O 3 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Education Groups (2 of 2), 02/07/2007-08/15/2007; O 3 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - COFHE, 11/09/2006-06/26/2007; O 3.1 (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - APRU, 09/08/2006-08/28/2007; O 3.4 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - AAAS, 09/19/2006-08/21/2007; O 3.7 (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - American Council on Education, 09/12/2006-08/29/2007; O 3.8 (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - The National Academies, 09/06/2006-08/15/2007; O 3.43 (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - NCAA, 09/05/2006-08/23/2007; O 3.44 (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Pacific Ten Conference, 09/02/2005-08/28/2007; O 3.47 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Universities Research Association, 10/18/2006-01/12/2007; O 7.16 (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Universities & Colleges, Misc. (1 of 3), 09/05/2006-01/30/2007; O 8 (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Universities & Colleges, Misc. (2 of 3), 02/05/2007-05/03/2007; O 8 (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - Universities & Colleges, Misc. (3 of 3), 05/03/2007-08/30/2007; O 8 (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - University of California, 09/05/2006-08/27/2007; O 8.43 (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Research Misc./Dean of Research, 09/12/2006-08/20/2007; R 0 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Student Groups, Misc., 09/08/2006-07/19/2007; ST 1.1 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Parent/Student Correspondence, 09/26/2006-07/31/2007; ST 8 (Box 7, Folder 121)
- President's records, 2007-2008; Accession ARCH-2010-044
  - Provost's Office, 10/09/2007-03/04/2008; AA 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dean of Chapel, 09/10/2007; AA 1.8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Education, 09/26/2007-03/10/2008; AA 1.13 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Emeriti, 10/16/2006-07/22/2008; AA 2.2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Development/Affairs, 09/04/2007-06/11/2008; AA 2.7 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Undergraduate Education, 09/11/2007-08/13/2008; AA 3 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Accreditation Issues, 11/05/2007-06/26/2008; AA 3.4 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ratings/Rankings, 10/02/2007-05/02/2008; AA 3.5 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Continuing Studies, 12/19/2007; AA 3.6 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Humanities & Sciences, School of, 09/07/2007-08/25/2008; AA 4.1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - SIEPR, 12/18/2007-08/27/2008; AA 4.1.20/1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Hopkins Marine Station, 10/04/2006-08/21/2008; AA 4.1.28 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Music, Dept. of, 10/04/2007-07/31/2008; AA 4.1.29 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Athletics, Dept. of, 10/25/2002-08/27/2008; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - GSB, 11/26/2007-08/18/2008; AA 4.2 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Engineering, School of, 10/30/2007-06/04/2008; AA 4.4 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Education, School of, 09/21/2007-07/09/2008; AA 4.5 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Hoover Institution, 06/15/2007-07/21/2008; AA 4.9 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - CISAC, 05/01/2007-03/12/2008; AA 4.10.6 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - SULAIR, 09/07/2007-08/19/2008; AA 4.12 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Law, School of, 11/18/2007-08/22/2008; AA 4.15 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Awards & Prizes, Misc., 08/27/2007-08/06/2008; AA 5 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Grants & Scholarships, Miscellaneous, 09/08/2005-08/18/2008; AA 6 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Fellowships, Miscellaneous, 10/02/2007-05/23/2008; AA 8 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Fulbright Fellowship/Scholarships, 10/26/2007-01/30/2008; AA 8.16 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Tanner Lectures, 03/21/2008-06/30/2008; AA 9.19 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Stanford Historical Society, 09/20/2006-04/25/2007; AD 1.2 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - ROTC, 09/21/2007-08/19/2008; AD 2.26 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, General, 09/12/2007-08/19/2008; AD 4.20 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - News articles, 11/15/2007-07/29/2008; AD 4.20.1 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Appreciation Letters, 09/04/2007-08/28/2008; AD 4.20.4/1 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Invitations (1 of 2), 09/07/2007-02/27/2008; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Invitations (2 of 2), 02/27/2008-08/25/2008; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Nonsense, 09/04/2007-08/25/2008; AD 4.20.5 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Recommendation Letters, 09/04/2007-06/30/2008; AD 4.20.6 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Complaint Letters, 10/02/2007-08/25/2008; AD 4.20.7 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Solicitations (1 of 4), 02/04/2007-11/30/2007; AD 4.20.8 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Solicitations (2 of 4), 12/02/2007-04/08/2008; AD 4.20.8 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Solicitations (3 of 4), 04/08/2008-05/20/2008; AD 4.20.8 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Solicitations (4 of 4), 05/20/2008-08/28/2008; AD 4.20.8 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - University Communications, 04/26/2007-08/11/2008; AD 4.22 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Campus Relations, 10/03/2005-06/30/2008; AD 6 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Admissions (1 of 2), 10/27/2006-04/25/2008; AD 8.1 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Admissions (2 of 2), 04/29/2008-08/25/2008; AD 8.1 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Student Affairs, 04/23/2007-08/25/2008; AD 8.8 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Bing Overseas Studies, 11/08/2007-08/19/2008; AD 8.11 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Financial Aid, 11/30/2007-08/04/2008; AD 8.12 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, 10/15/2007-07/29/2008; AD 8.18 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Registrar, 11/07/2007-06/20/2008; AD 8.21 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Human Resources, 09/04/2007-07/14/2008; AD 10 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - SLAC/CLJ, 02/06/2008-05/23/2008; AD 10-SLAC/CLJ (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Employment Inquiries, 10/02/2007-08/27/2008; AD 10.1 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Media & Publications Misc., 10/17/2007-08/21/2008; AD 11.8 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Media & Publications (internal), 11/14/2007-7/14/2008; AD 11.8.11 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Business Affairs, CFO, 05/23/2007-03/27/2008; AD 12.2 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Tuition, 01/11/2008-03/05/2008; AD 12.5.4 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Land, BLDGS & Real Estate, 10/09/2007-08/26/2008; AD 12.14 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Parking & Transportation, 01/10/2006-07/16/2008; AD 12.14.7/53 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Conferences, Misc., 09/20/2007-08/20/2008; AD 13.10.1 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Alumni Relations, 09/24/2007-03/31/2008; AL 1 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Alumni Correspondence (1 of 2), 09/04/2007-12/31/2007; AL 1.3 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Alumni Correspondence (2 of 2), 12/31/2007-08/24/2008; AL 1.3 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Alumni Events, 09/20/2006-08/25/2008; AL 1.7 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Board of Trustees, Misc., 07/24/2003-08/28/2008; B 1 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - University Committees, 01/30/2002-05/18/2007; C 6 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Government/Community Rel., 07/03/2006-07/01/2008; G 1 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - California State Government, 01/23/2007-07/17/2008; G 1.2 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - U.S. Government, 7/30/2007-08/21/2008; G 3 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Foreign Government Relations, 09/04/2007-08/19/2008; G 5 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - CIFPR, 09/07/2007-08/05/2008; G 7 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 11/20/2007-07/24/2008; G 10 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Lucile Packard Children's Hospital, 09/04/2007-04/29/2008; SHS 7 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - School of Medicine Administration, 04/20/2005-08/06/2008; M 1 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Misc. Organizations (1 of 2), 09/15/2006-04/28/2008; O 1 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Misc. Organizations (2 of 2), 04/28/2008-08/28/2008; O 1 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Education Groups, Misc., 08/01/2007-08/12/2008; O 3 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - APRU, 10/02/2007-07/24/2008; O 3.4 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - AAAS, 09/05/2007-08/12/2008; O 3.7 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - American Council on Education, 09/11/2007-07/15/2008; O 3.8 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - NAICU, 09/01/2006-07/09/2008; O 3.10 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - The College Board, 09/07/2006-07/28/2008; O 3.25 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - The National Academies, 09/11/2007-08/12/2008; O 3.43 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - NCAA, 10/19/2005-08/25/2008; O 3.44 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Pacific Ten Conference, 09/11/2007-08/27/2008; O 3.47 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Athletic Organizations, Misc., 09/12/2006-06/25/2008; O 4 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Universities Research Association, 10/19/2007-07/14/2008; O 7.16 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Universities & Colleges, Misc. (1 of 2), 09/08/2005-04/14/2008; O 8 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Universities & Colleges, Misc. (2 of 2), 04/14/2008-08/27/2008; O 8 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - AAU, 09/12/2006-08/27/2008; O 8.7 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum, 09/08/2006-08/18/2008; O 11 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Research Misc./Dean of Research, 10/17/2007-08/20/2008; R 0 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Students, Misc., 10/03/2006-02/01/2008; ST 1 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Student Groups, Misc., 05/03/2007-06/11/2008; ST 1.1 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - ASSU, 01/16/2007-07/02/2008; ST 2 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Parent/Student Correspondence, 09/04/2007-08/24/2008; ST 8 (Box 5, Folder 95)
- President's records, 2008-2009; Accession ARCH-2011-074
  Access to Collection
  Restricted 20 years from end of tenure of president Hennessy.
  - Provost's Office, 38454; AA 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Education, 10/20/2008-04/17/2009; AA 1.13 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Development/Affairs, 09/16/2008-05/12/2009; AA 2.7 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Education, 11/25/2008-03/25/2009; AA 3 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Accreditation Issues, 09/16/2008-07/09/2009; AA 3.4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ratings/Rankings, 05/12/2008-01/15/2009; AA 3.5 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Humanities and Sciences, School of, 12/15/2008-08/19/2009; AA 4.1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Humanities Center, 10/09/2008-11/12/2008; AA 4.1.1/2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - SIEPR, 12/09/2008-01/30/2009; AA 4.1.20/1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - History, Department of, 10/05/2006-08/26/2009; AA 4.1.25 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Hopkins Marine Station, 05/07/2009-05/19/2009; AA 4.1.28 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Athletics, Dept. of, 08/09/2007-08/31/2009; AA 4.1.30 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Football Games, 09/04/2007-08/04/2009; AA 4.1.30/1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Physics, Department of, 04/26/2007-02/04/2009; AA 4.1.33 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - GSB, 10/15/2008-07/21/2009; AA 4.2 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Education, School of, 09/19/2008-04/17/2009; AA 4.5 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Hoover Institution, 11/25/2008-08/05/2009; AA 4.9 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - SULAIR, 11/04/2008-07/15/2009; AA 4.12 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Law, School of, 10/28/2008-08/31/2009; AA 4.15 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Awards and Prizes, Misc., 09/03/2008-07/28/2009; AA 5 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Grants and Scholarships, Miscellaneous, 09/05/2008-08/26/2009; AA 6 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Fellowships, Miscellaneous, 09/23/2008-06/12/2009; AA 8 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Fulbright Fellowship/Scholarships, 10/23/2008-06/04/2009; AA 8.16 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Fellowship, 04/10/2007-04/08/2008; AA 8.17 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Knight Fellowships/Foundation, 09/11/2006-08/31/2009; AA 8.25 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - ROTC, 09/16/2008-03/27/2009; AD 2.26 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, General, 09/08/2008-06/08/2009; AD 4.20 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - News articles, 09/11/2008-05/29/2009; AD 4.20.1 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 12/17/2007-01/05/2009; AD 4.20.3 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Appreciation Letters, 09/02/2008-08/31/2009; AD 4.20.4/1 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Invitations, 05/07/2007-08/31/2009; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Nonsense, 01/08/2008-08/31/2009; AD 4.20.5 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Recommendation Letters, 11/07/2006-08/18/2009; AD 4.20.6 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Complaint Letters, 10/06/2008-08/19/2009; AD 4.20.7 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Solicitations (1 of 4), 09/04/2008-11/12/2008; AD 4.20.8 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Solicitations (2 of 4), 11/13/2008-01/08/2009; AD 4.20.8 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Solicitations (3 of 4), 01/12/2009-05/06/2009; AD 4.20.8 (Box 2, Folder 5)